<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Star Wars - Factions</name>
  <author>Xen and Jecrell</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>projectjedi.factions</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
      <displayName>JecsTools</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/932008009</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://patreon.com/jecrell</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>https://discordapp.com/api/webhooks/513416032690372618/SYHfStkpTbun9iA6gxwQ7vLVU5m-ldiiM6dRrbwVGGYRVBQJJWwtCP_VsTWjk-RAgfn5 (02-29-2020)

	C# Programming by Jecrell.
	C# updates, Art Assets, and XML by Xen.

	Other contributors:
	Berengar
	SmartCheeta

	Patreon Patrons:
	Jedi Master Ailan, Shane Malley, Michin, TheDayDude, Dakota Pohlman, Falloutmonk, Legless, Slick Liquid,  Don Butterblume, Karol Rybak, Mathias Broxvall, Nemuri Hime, Hannah Forster, Christian Hermansen, NiNe Bottles of Rum, Populous25, Steven James, Marcus Sireanu, Michael Lauder, Thom Black

Thank you to my Patrons for supporting me in my efforts. Without you, none of this would be possible.

These are the most excellent rim dwellers who support me: 
Marcus Bell, RainerWingel, Dalton Johnson, Chris Seieroe, Robin Gleeson, Robert Alessi, Lea Stannard, Teres, David Silberstein, Sam, Kiya Nicoll, Matt Harris, Paul Fenwick, Grendalloffen, Don Homer, Josh McCabe, Elodie, Gothi, J, Michael Paugh, Audrin Navarro, Михаил Юрченко, Calum, Tim Stillson, Adam Bliss, Populous25, Marcus Sireanu, Maaxar, John Kanady, Midgeman, Dick Jones, Patrick, TinyFloatingTurtle, Nathan Getman, LionsFate, Sharp Spook, Cristina Shaver, Mark, George Chong Chuang Ming, Oliver White, roxxploxx, Emily Shaw, Karol Rybak, Justin Andres, Marcus Regan, Robin Hager, Allic, Austin Harbert, E_T, Alex Mederer, Alexander, Toss Antilles

========================
Changelog
========================
https://discordapp.com/api/webhooks/513416032690372618/SYHfStkpTbun9iA6gxwQ7vLVU5m-ldiiM6dRrbwVGGYRVBQJJWwtCP_VsTWjk-RAgfn5 (02-29-2020)
========================
RimWorld has been updated to version 1.1. Star Wars Factions needed to have some revisions to match the new changes to RimWorld. Factions are now properly hostile on start. When refusing to pay taxes, imperials will become hostile.

1.20.0.1 (02-05-2019)
========================
No longer uses Building and WorkTable as abstracts

1.20.0.0 (10-19-2018)
========================
Initial update for RimWorld 1.0.

</description>
</ModMetaData>